<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <description>James Gorman, chairman and chief executive of Morgan Stanley, saw a 7% raise for 2016, while Goldman Sachs cut stock awards for several executives after revenue fell 9%.</description>
      <link>http://www.wsj.com/article/SB10782002109759823356104582571722419410772.html</link>
      <title>Morgan Stanley Gives CEO a Raise; Goldman Trims Stock-Pay for Some</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 05:39:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>The historic U.S. election jolted Wall Street trading desks, buoying investor confidence and sparking activity that pushed the five biggest U.S. investment banks to sharply higher fourth-quarter profits.</description>
      <link>http://www.wsj.com/article/SB10782002109759823356104582567713271892678.html</link>
      <title>Wall Street Gets Back Its Groove</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 11:59:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>Goldman Sachs easily beat analyst expectations, turning in a fourth quarter that was among the strongest on Wall Street.</description>
      <link>http://www.wsj.com/article/SB12688685040638893401304582565700228322124.html</link>
      <title>Goldman Sachs Results Surge on Trading Bounce</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 02:50:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>Alan Cohen, Goldman Sachs Group Inc.’s head of compliance and the longest-serving internal cop on Wall Street, is vacating his seat after 13 years.</description>
      <link>http://www.wsj.com/article/SB12598667311001443700204582565532863347536.html</link>
      <title>Goldman’s Compliance Chief Moves On</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 09:10:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>Goldman Sachs Group Inc. is scheduled to report results for the fourth quarter and year on Wednesday before markets open. The New York investment bank is expected to report higher earnings and revenue for the quarter.</description>
      <link>http://blogs.wsj.com/briefly/2017/01/17/5-things-to-watch-in-goldman-sachss-results-2/</link>
      <title>5 Things to Watch in Goldman Sachs’ Results</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 02:43:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>Morgan Stanley posted its best fourth-quarter results since the financial crisis, keeping a lid on expenses and growing revenue in both its core Wall Street businesses and its newer wealth franchise.</description>
      <link>http://www.wsj.com/article/SB11776928018298894384504582561774028243102.html</link>
      <title>Morgan Stanley Posts Biggest Fourth-Quarter Profit Since Crisis</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 11:47:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>Morgan Stanley is due to report fourth-quarter and annual results on Tuesday before the markets open. Here's what you should watch:</description>
      <link>http://blogs.wsj.com/briefly/2017/01/15/5-things-to-watch-in-morgan-stanleys-results-3/</link>
      <title>5 Things to Watch in Morgan Stanley’s Results</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 05:05:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>Rajeev Misra, who built Deutsche Bank’s credit-derivatives business in the 2000s, is a leader on SoftBank chief Masayoshi Son’s next big thing: a $100 billion fund to invest in futuristic technologies.</description>
      <link>http://www.wsj.com/article/SB11008264203904724577704582551560526583408.html</link>
      <title>The Wall Street Trader Behind SoftBank’s $100 Billion Fund</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 05:37:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>Goldman Sachs named Elisha Wiesel as its new chief information officer, the bank’s top-ranking technology officer.</description>
      <link>http://www.wsj.com/article/SB12051942542359674776004582549612044387898.html</link>
      <title>Goldman Sachs Names Top-Ranking Technology Officer</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 04:58:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>After tapping several Goldman Sachs Group Inc. alumni for senior economic posts, President-elect Donald Trump’s team is considering yet another for a key job at the Treasury Department.</description>
      <link>http://www.wsj.com/article/SB12484812745623853734404582543640333261480.html</link>
      <title>Trump Team Considering Another Goldman Executive for Key Treasury Post</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 05:55:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>Goldman Sachs has added Julian Salisbury, who runs a unit that invests the bank’s own money, to its powerful management committee. Mr. Salisbury’s elevation comes during speculation that some regulations might be pared back under a Trump administration.</description>
      <link>http://www.wsj.com/article/SB12484812745623853734404582541391279520500.html</link>
      <title>Goldman Elevates Special-Situations Chief as Deregulation Looms</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 04:00:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>Apple confirmed it plans to invest $1 billion in SoftBank’s new technology fund to help finance technologies it could use in the future.</description>
      <link>http://www.wsj.com/article/SB12484812745623853734404582539240544355230.html</link>
      <title>Apple Confirms Its $1 Billion Investment in SoftBank Fund</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 12:14:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump nominates Sullivan &amp; Cromwell law partner Jay Clayton as Securities and Exchange Commission chairman, adding another figure with close Wall Street ties to Mr. Trump’s administration.</description>
      <link>http://www.wsj.com/article/SB12484812745623853734404582539100056792734.html</link>
      <title>SEC Pick Clayton Is a 180 From Chairman White</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 06:43:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>SoftBank Group has lined up chip maker Qualcomm as an investor in the Japanese firm’s new technology fund, helping the portfolio reach its $100 billion goal, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
      <link>http://www.wsj.com/article/SB11501294962522924743304582536952635667814.html</link>
      <title>Qualcomm to Invest in SoftBank’s Technology Fund</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 10:01:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>While Goldman Sachs this week underwent its most dramatic management reshuffling in a decade, Lloyd Blankfein remains firmly ensconced as chief executive.</description>
      <link>http://www.wsj.com/article/SB11421146617080193814604582501272907358482.html</link>
      <title>The Real Winner in Goldman’s Management Reshuffle</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2016 09:06:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>Goldman Sachs Group has raised $4.5 billion for its new private-equity fund, nearing the low end of its goal, with additional fundraising expected early next year.</description>
      <link>http://www.wsj.com/article/SB11421146617080193814604582500871080080362.html</link>
      <title>Goldman Sachs Raises $4.5 Billion for Buyouts Fund</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 11:14:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>Credit Suisse Group AG has hired a new head of equities from UBS Group AG, hoping to reinvigorate its stock-trading business and better ply that service to global billionaires .</description>
      <link>http://www.wsj.com/article/SB11421146617080193814604582498574051685832.html</link>
      <title>Credit Suisse Hires New Stock-Trading Head from UBS</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 08:26:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>Goldman Sachs is revamping its network of investment bankers, shifting partners away from New York and to places like Dallas. The move is aimed at developing brokers and improving relations with clients.</description>
      <link>http://www.wsj.com/article/SB11421146617080193814604582497250234333194.html</link>
      <title>Goldman Sachs Looks to Spread Banker Web Beyond New York</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 05:30:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>Exxon Mobil’s board faces a difficult decision over how to make a financial break with Chief Executive Rex Tillerson, who will step down as chief executive at year’s end now that Donald Trump has chosen him as secretary of state.</description>
      <link>http://www.wsj.com/article/SB11421146617080193814604582496781345231606.html</link>
      <title>Exxon Faces Dilemma on Rex Tillerson’s Pay</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 06:25:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <description>Goldman Sachs will elevate David Solomon and Harvey Schwartz to be top lieutenants to CEO Lloyd Blankfein, filling a void left by No. 2 executive Gary Cohn, who is leaving the bank to join the Trump administration.</description>
      <link>http://www.wsj.com/article/SB11324270286969644715704582495723656131082.html</link>
      <title>Goldman Sachs Names David Solomon, Harvey Schwartz to Succeed Gary Cohn</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 01:20:00 EST</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

